<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>System Integration - ERP accounting to e-commerce and B2B on Stock2Shop</title>
    <link>/integrations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in System Integration - ERP accounting to e-commerce and B2B on Stock2Shop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WooCommerce</title>
      <link>/integrations/woo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/woo/</guid>
      <description>An open-source e-commerce plug-in for WordPress that’s customisable and streamlined for retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woocommerce</title>
      <link>/integrations/woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>An open-source e-commerce plug-in for WordPress that’s customisable and streamlined for retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Trade Store</title>
      <link>/integrations/b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/b2b/</guid>
      <description>Our very own wholesale platform and shopping cart. Manage multiple price lists as well as warehouse and product data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE Business Cloud Accounting</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage1/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage One: Simple and secure online accounting software</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud accounting (formerly sage one)</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-one-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-one-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage One: Simple and secure online accounting software</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE Business Cloud Financials</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage2/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Live: A new business management and accounting solution for growing enterprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials (formerly sage live) integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Live: A new business management and accounting solution for growing enterprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE 50Cloud Pastel Express</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage3/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Partner Xpress Advantage: Harness the power and productivity of a trusted desktop solution that integrate with Microsoft Office 365.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE 50Cloud Pastel Partner</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage4/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Pastel Partner: This tried and tested accounting software includes direct bank feeds and many useful cloud features to help you boost productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel partner (formerly sage pastel partner) integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/pastel-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/pastel-partner/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Pastel Partner: This tried and tested accounting software includes direct bank feeds and many useful cloud features to help you boost productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE 100 Evolution</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage5/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Evolution Standard: Ideal for growing companies to manage products, orders, customers, finances and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution (formerly sage evolution standard) integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-pastel-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-pastel-evolution/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Evolution Standard: Ideal for growing companies to manage products, orders, customers, finances and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE 200 Evolution</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage6/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Evolution Premium: Get back to basics with smart, cost-effective software for big businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAGE 300cloud</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage7/</guid>
      <description>A streamlined and efficient solution for small to mid-market companies with up to several hundred users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud (formerly sage accpac) Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-formerly-sage-accpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-formerly-sage-accpac/</guid>
      <description>A streamlined and efficient solution for small to mid-market companies with up to several hundred users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>syspro integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/syspro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/syspro/</guid>
      <description>SYSPRO is an independent ERP provider, taking a simplified approach to ensuring success for manufacturers and distributors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omni Accounts</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni/</guid>
      <description>Omni Accounts is an “all-in-one” accounting system that delivers focused, effective enterprise resource planning and business solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Omni Accounts is an “all-in-one” accounting system that delivers focused, effective enterprise resource planning and business solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ Retail</title>
      <link>/integrations/retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/retail/</guid>
      <description>IQ Retail gives you business accounting and management solutions designed to work in a retail, distributive and hospitality environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Dynamics NAV</title>
      <link>/integrations/dynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dynamics/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Dynamics NAV helps SMEs and large international groups manage their accounting and finances, supply chain, and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parcelninja</title>
      <link>/integrations/parcelninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/parcelninja/</guid>
      <description>Run your e-commerce business from anywhere with ParcelNinja’s scalable, outsourced warehousing and fulfillment solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/integrations/integrate-sage-with-ecommerce-b2b-trade-stores-and-online-marketplaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/integrate-sage-with-ecommerce-b2b-trade-stores-and-online-marketplaces/</guid>
      <description>Content to follow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SAP business One Magento Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-magento/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SAP business one woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product data from SAP Business One to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from SAP Business One. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SYSPRO  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/syspro-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/syspro-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from SYSPRO to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between SYSPRO and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SYSPRO magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/syspro-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/syspro-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Sync your product information – including images, warehouses, price lists and more – easily and quickly from SYSPRO to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between SYSPRO and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SYSPRO shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/syspro-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/syspro-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from SYSPRO to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from SYSPRO to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between SYSPRO and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.. Once you’ve configured products correctly on SYSPRO (we can help), fields from SYSPRO can be “mapped” to any attribute on Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SYSPRO takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-syspro-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-syspro-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from SYSPRO to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on SYSPRO (we can help), price lists and stock levels from SYSPRO can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SYSPRO woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/syspro-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/syspro-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from SYSPRO to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from SYSPRO. You can also easily sync your images between SYSPRO and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Trade Store</title>
      <link>/integrations/b2b-shopping-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/b2b-shopping-cart/</guid>
      <description>Our very own wholesale platform and shopping cart. Manage multiple price lists as well as warehouse and product data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dolfin</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin/</guid>
      <description>Dolfin Point of Sale and Merchandising presents a customisable ERP solution to meet Fashion, Apparel and General Merchandise retailer’s needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolfin B2B Trade Store</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, you can sync inventory and customer data from Dolfin to your B2B trade store.
 Sync your product information from Dolfin to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Dolfin and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolfin Magento</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Syncing product information from Dolfin to Magento is easy once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Dolfin and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolfin Parcelninja</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-parcelninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-parcelninja/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolfin Shopify</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Integrate Dolfin and Shopify, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to streamline your workflow, simplify the ordering process and save time - and money. Find out more about how a Dolfin, Shopify Integration can help your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolfin Takealot</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-takealot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-takealot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dolfin woocommerce</title>
      <link>/integrations/dolfin-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/dolfin-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You can sync product data easily and quickly from Dolfin to WooCommerce – near real time, with no risk of human error.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Dolfin. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iQ Retail  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/iq-retail-b2b-trade-store-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/iq-retail-b2b-trade-store-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from iQ Retail to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between iQ Retail and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iq retail integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/iq-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/iq-retail/</guid>
      <description>IQ Retail gives you business accounting and management solutions designed to work in a retail, distributive and hospitality environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iQ Retail magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/iq-retail-magento-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/iq-retail-magento-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from iQ Retail to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between iQ Retail and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ retail shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/iq-retail-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/iq-retail-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from iQ Retail to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from iQ Retail to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between iQ Retail and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iQ Retail takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-iq-retail-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-iq-retail-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from IQ Retail to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on IQ Retail (we can help), price lists and stock levels from IQ Retail can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ retail WooCommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/iq-retail-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/iq-retail-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from iQ Retail to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from iQ Retail. You can also easily sync your images between iQ Retail and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/isync-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/isync-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You can sync inventory data with ease once you’ve integrated iSync and your B2B trade store.
 Sync your product information from iSync to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between iSync and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/isync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/isync/</guid>
      <description>iSync is the comprehensive ERP &amp;amp; PLM software solution designed specifically for the apparel industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/isync-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/isync-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from iSync to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between iSync and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/isync-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/isync-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Ensure all your inventory data is consistent across your various channels. You’ll be able to:
 Sync your product information from iSync to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between iSync and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.. Once you’ve configured products correctly on iSync (we can help), fields from iSync can be “mapped” to any attribute on Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-isync-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-isync-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from iSync to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on iSync (we can help), price lists and stock levels from iSync can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>isync woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/isync-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/isync-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You can easily sync your product information from iSync to WooCommerce once they’re integrated with each other.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from iSync. You can also easily sync your images between iSync and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento</title>
      <link>/integrations/magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/magento/</guid>
      <description>A powerful open-source e-commerce platform with B2B features scaled for complex data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microsoft dynamics nav  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/ms-navision-b2b-trade-store-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/ms-navision-b2b-trade-store-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from Microsoft Dynamics NAV to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Microsoft Dynamics NAV and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microsoft dynamics nav integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/ms-navision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/ms-navision/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Dynamics NAV helps SMEs and large international groups manage their accounting and finances, supply chain, and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microsoft dynamics nav magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/ms-navision-magento-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/ms-navision-magento-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from Microsoft Dynamics NAV to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Microsoft Dynamics NAV and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microsoft dynamics nav shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/ms-navision-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/ms-navision-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from Microsoft Dynamics NAV to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from Microsoft Dynamics NAV to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Microsoft Dynamics NAV and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>microsoft dynamics nav woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/ms-navision-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/ms-navision-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from Microsoft Dynamics NAV to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Microsoft Dynamics NAV. You can also easily sync your images between Microsoft Dynamics NAV and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS navision takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-ms-navision-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-ms-navision-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from MS Navision to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on MS Navision (we can help), price lists and stock levels from MS Navision can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni-accounts-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni-accounts-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data from Omni Accounts to your B2B trade store – simply and without the risk of human error.
 Sync your product information from Omni Accounts to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Omni Accounts and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni-accounts-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni-accounts-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data It’s simple to sync inventory data – product information and images – once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Omni Accounts and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni-accounts-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni-accounts-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data It’s easy to sync inventory data – product information and images – once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Omni Accounts to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Omni Accounts and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-omni-accounts-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-omni-accounts-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Omni Accounts to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Omni Accounts (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Omni Accounts can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omni accounts woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/omni-accounts-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/omni-accounts-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Sync product data near real time, with no risk of human error from Omni Accounts to WooCommerce, once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Omni Accounts. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>parcelninja</title>
      <link>/integrations/parcel-ninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/parcel-ninja/</guid>
      <description>Run your e-commerce business from anywhere with ParcelNinja’s scalable, outsourced warehousing and fulfillment solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-evolution-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-evolution-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, you can sync inventory and customer data from Sage 100 Evolution (formerly Sage Evolution Standard) to your B2B trade store.
 Sync your product information from Sage 100 Evolution to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 100 Evolution and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-evolution-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-evolution-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Syncing product information from Sage 100 Evolution (formerly Sage Evolution Standard) to Magento is easy once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage 100 Evolution and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-evolution-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-evolution-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You can sync inventory data with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 100 Evolution (formerly Sage Evolution Standard) to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 100 Evolution and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-evolution-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-evolution-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 100 Evolution to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage 100 Evolution (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage 100 Evolution can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 100 evolution woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-evolution-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-evolution-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You can sync product data easily and quickly from Sage 100 Evolution (formerly Sage Evolution Standard) to WooCommerce – near real time, with no risk of human error.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage 100 Evolution. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution (formerly sage evolution premium)</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Evolution Premium: Get back to basics with smart, cost-effective software for big businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-magento-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-magento-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from Sage 200 Evolution (Formerly Sage Evolution Premium) to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage 200 Evolution and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from Sage 200 Evolution (Formerly Sage Evolution Premium) to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from Sage 200 Evolution to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 200 Evolution and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-takealot-marketplace-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-takealot-marketplace-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 200 Evolution to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage 200 Evolution (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage 200 Evolution can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-b2b-trade-store-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-b2b-trade-store-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from Sage 200 Evolution to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 200 Evolution and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 200 evolution woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-200-evolution-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from Sage 200 Evolution to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage 200 Evolution. You can also easily sync your images between Sage 200 Evolution and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-b2b-trade-store-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-b2b-trade-store-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from Sage 300cloud to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 300cloud and your B2B trade store, all from your central console. And you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-magento-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-magento-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from Sage 300cloud to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage 300cloud and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from Sage 300cloud to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from Sage 300cloud to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 300cloud and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-takealot-marketplace-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-takealot-marketplace-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 300cloud to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage 300cloud (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage 300cloud can be “mapped” to price, arecommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 300cloud woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-300cloud-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-300cloud-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from Sage 300cloud to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage 300cloud. You can also easily sync your images between Sage 300cloud and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel partner  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Syncing inventory and customer data is simple and straightforward once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel partner magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data It’s a simple process to sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner (formerly Sage pastel Partner) to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel partner shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Syncing inventory data is simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner (we can help), fields from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner can be “mapped” to any attribute on Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel partner woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-pastel-partner-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product data from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner (formerly Sage Pastel partner) to WooCommerce, and keep it updated near real time.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Partner. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-b2b-trade-store-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-b2b-trade-store-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data Sync inventory and customer data to reduce the chance of human error.
 Sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress (formerly sage partner xpress)</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress/</guid>
      <description>Formerly Sage Partner Xpress Advantagse: Harness the power and productivity of a trusted desktop solution that integrate with Microsoft Office 365.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-magento-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-magento-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily and quickly sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress (Formerly Sage Pastel Xpress Advantage) to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-shopify-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-shopify-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your inventory data – products, images, warehouses and more – from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress (Formerly Sage Pastel Xpress Advantage) to Shopify.
 Sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-takealot-marketplace-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-takealot-marketplace-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage 50cloud pastel xpress woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-woocommerce-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-50cloud-pastel-xpress-woocommerce-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Easily sync your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress (Formerly Sage Pastel Xpress Advantage) to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress. You can also easily sync your images between Sage 50cloud Pastel Xpress and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage accounting takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-accounting-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-accounting-integration/</guid>
      <description>SYNC DATA You can sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage Accounting (formerly Sage One) to the Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Accounting (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage Accounting can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud accounting  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-one-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-one-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Accounting (formerly Sage One) to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage Business Cloud Accounting and your B2B trade store, all from your central console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud accounting magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-one-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-one-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You can sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Accounting (formerly Sage One) to Magento with ease – and with no risk of human error.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Syncing images between Sage Business Cloud Accounting and Magento is also simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud accounting shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-one-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-one-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Syncing inventory data is simple once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Accounting (formerly Sage One) to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). You can also easily sync your images between Sage Business Cloud Accounting and Shopify, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud accounting woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-one-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-one-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Simply and seamlessly sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Accounting (formerly Sage One) to WooCommerce.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage Business Cloud Accounting. You can also easily sync your images between Sage Business Cloud Accounting and WooCommerce, and you can upload or remove images automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials  B2B trade store integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You can sync inventory and customer data from Sage Business Cloud Financials (formerly Sage Live) to your B2B trade store, so there’s always only one set of data, updated near real time.
 Sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Financials to your B2B trade store. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Business Cloud Financials (we can help), fields from Sage Business Cloud Financials can be “mapped” to any attribute on your B2B trade store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials magento integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-magento/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data One of the most essential parts of integration: being able to sync product information with ease from Sage Business Cloud Financials (formerly Sage Live) to Magento.
 Details like the SKU, price, stock level and product title will all be synced with Stock2Shop, so that your product data is always up-to-date. Products can also be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Business Cloud Financials (we can help), fields from Sage Business Cloud Financials can be “mapped” to any attribute on Magento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials shopify integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data You’ll be able to sync inventory data with ease once you’ve integrated Sage Business Cloud Financials (formerly Sage Live) and Shopify.
 Sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Financials to Shopify. This includes the SKU, price, stock availability and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes). Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Business Cloud Financials (we can help), fields from Sage Business Cloud Financials can be “mapped” to any attribute on Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-financials-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-financials-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage Business Cloud Financials to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Business Cloud Financials (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage Business Cloud Financials can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage business cloud financials woocommerce integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sage-business-cloud-financials-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>Sync inventory data Syncing product data is an essential first step – you’ll be able to sync data from Sage Business Cloud Financials (formerly Sage Live) to WooCommerce with ease, and near real time.
 Instead of manually inputting data and any necessary changes to that data – which opens you up to the risk of human error – you can sync all your product information from Sage Financials. This data includes the SKU, price, stock level and product title, and can be updated on schedule (up to every 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sage pastel partner takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-pastel-partner-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sage-pastel-partner-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from Sage Pastel Partner to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on Sage Pastel Partner (we can help), price lists and stock levels from Sage Pastel Partner can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business One B2B Trade Store Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-b2b-trade-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-b2b-trade-store/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP business one integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap/</guid>
      <description>ERP software designed to streamline key processes and provide real-time information to give you greater strategic insights, fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business One ParcelNinja Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-parcelninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-parcelninja/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business One Shopify Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-shopify/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business One Takealot Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-takealot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-takealot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business One Woocommerce Integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/sap-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/sap-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP takealot marketplace integration</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sap-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot-marketplace-sap-integration/</guid>
      <description>Sync data You’ll be able to sync inventory data and pricing with ease once you’ve integrated with Stock2Shop.
 Sync your product information from SAP to your Takealot marketplace. This includes the price, recommended retail price, lead time and stock availability, and can be updated near real time. Once you’ve configured products correctly on SAP (we can help), price lists and stock levels from SAP can be “mapped” to price, recommended retail price and delivery lead time for each of your Takealot marketplace offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shopify</title>
      <link>/integrations/shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/shopify/</guid>
      <description>Start selling today with a purpose-built and fast growing e-commerce platform that’s quick to launch and easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>takealot</title>
      <link>/integrations/takealot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/takealot/</guid>
      <description>Automatically update your important product information such as pricing, stock levels and delivery lead times on the Takealot marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Dolfin as a linked source</title>
      <link>/integrations/workflow-dolfin-shopify-linked-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/workflow-dolfin-shopify-linked-source/</guid>
      <description>TODO </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Dolfin to update stock only</title>
      <link>/integrations/workflow-dolfin-shopify-stock-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/integrations/workflow-dolfin-shopify-stock-only/</guid>
      <description>TODO </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
